小姐
Miss?
我得跟你道歉
I have to apologize.
不用跟我道歉 跟阿米什人道歉吧
Well, not to me, but I'm sure the Amish are pissed
你把他们的招牌打扮弄得基味十足
that you're gaying up their look.
我不够钱给你付小费
I don't have enough money for the tip.
怪了 你吃餐厅的辣椒没死
Weird. You survive the diner chili,
却要死在服务员的手里
and it's the waitress that kills you!
但我可以用别种方式给
But I can tip another way.
我是个灵媒
I'm a psychic.
所以你已经知道
So, uh, you already know
别人会发现你横尸何处
where they're gonna find your body.
少来了 我会死于桥梁坍塌
Oh, please. I die in a bridge collapse
跟你一点关系都没有
you have nothing to do with.
我能告诉你你的未来
I can tell you your future.
哈 那你错了 我没未来
Ha! You're wrong. I don't have one.
看到那个卡座的男人了吗
See the guy in the booth over there?
杰瑞德·"莱闹的"
Jared "Leto Himself Go"?
他说要帮我占卜未来当小费
He just offered to read my future as my tip!
哈 你都没未来
Ha! You don't have one.
小姐 让我帮你看手相
Miss, let me read your palm.
先生 你现在过来可不是个好主意
Sir, coming over here right now is not a good idea.
我们不喜欢被陌生人骗财骗色
We don't like to be stiffed by strangers.
再空虚六个月或许可以 但现在时候未到
In six months, maybe, but we're not there yet.
我不是骗子灵媒
I'm a legit psychic.
我算到长发会重新流行
I predicted long hair was coming back
所以我及时把头发留长了
in time to have long hair when it did.
行 你可以来看我的手相
Okay. You can read my palm.
我不介意听到些好消息
I could use some good news.
也真应该用用护手霜 抱歉啦
I could also use some hand moisturizer--sorry.
我看到两个"M"字
I see two Ms?
你个贱人 有MM巧克力豆居然不分我
You bitch! Have you been holding out on M&M's?
是不是指我旗下的"魔"性男"模"特
Is it the male model I'm managing
还跟"麦"克斯"摸"来摸去的那位
who's also making it with Max?
其实 我看到了一个小小的失败
Actually...I see a small failure.
我把话收回 你可真准
I take it back. You are good!
你的巧克力柠檬碎蛋糕
Here's your chocolate lemon crumble.
这口味乍听不搭 结果居然很搭
Sounds like it shouldn't work together, but it does.
就像爵士大师跟雷帝嘎嘎合作的糕点版
It's the Tony Bennett and Lady Gaga of desserts.
麦克斯 我能不能就吃一口
Max, can I have just a wee bite?
碎蛋糕的蛋糕碎
A crumble of the crumble?
卡洛琳什么都不让我吃
Caroline won't let me eat anything
因为今天有重要的棚拍
because of my big photo shoot.
快点吧
Hurry!
不许嚼 不许享受 吞就是了
No chewing, no enjoying. Just swallow.
给我吐出来
Spit that out!
不要
No!
我让你吐出来
I said spit that out!
你现在可是个模特 丢死人了
You're a model now! Shame on you!
贱人 他要饿死了
Bitch, he's starving.
他没有吃东西吧
He's not eating, is he?
我可不希望我女友的摄影棚
I don't want the Stay Puft Marshmallow man
出现一个肥肿胖死鬼
showing up at my girlfriend's photo shoot.
我从周二开始就没吃过东西了
I haven't eaten anything since Tuesday!
今天早上他还想偷吞牙膏
This morning, he tried to swallow his toothpaste,
但幸好我及时赶到阻止了他
but I was right there to stop him.
亲 干得漂亮
Good, honey.
就是这样的铁石心肠让我决定
That kind of heartlessness is why I've decided
要让你当嗨翻天新分店的经理
to make you the manager of our hot new location of the High.
天啊 这太棒了
Oh, my God! This is so exciting!
终于有人看到了我这一身潜力
Someone's finally realizing my full potential,
而且是除了我之外的人
and it's not me!
那我可以任命麦克斯当首席烘焙师吗
Will I be able to make Max head pastry chef?
你这新分店是开在哪里
And where is this new location?
目前一切都还不公开[层层包起]
Well, right now, everything's under wraps
就像六个月前的我的脸一样
the way my face was six months ago.
但做为经理 你有权聘请任何班底
But as manager, you can hire your own staff,
我也允许你挖角麦克斯
and I'll even let you poach Max.
我再告诉你 新分店超赞
I'll also tell you the new spot is amazing.
国际化 还位在交通枢纽
It's international. It's a hub.
绝对是旗舰级的
I'm talking major flagship.
亲 我知道你要爽翻了
Honey, I get that you're happy,
但是请别再跟我对视了好吗
but enough with the eye contact.
没人可以直视本后的双眼
No one can look me in the eye.
我就是穿着香奈儿的美杜莎
I'm the Medusa in Chanel.
做爱的时候 麦克斯也不许我看着她眼睛
Max doesn't let me look her in the eyes during sex either.
我说了 对视要额外收费
I told you, eye contact's extra.
麦克斯 你听到了吗
Max, did you hear that?
旗舰级
Major flagship!
有人说我是旗舰级尤物吗
Uh, did someone just call me a major flag?
我听到你说了 如果你的新店
I think you did, and if I don't get to
不聘请我
go to the new place with you two,
我就要跟HR[人事部]说
I'm telling HR.
就是我的心理医生 海克特·罗德里奎兹的缩写
That's Hector Rodriguez, my therapist.
你有兴趣来嗨翻天新分店
Would you be interested in coming to the new High
加入我们的团队吗
as part of our team?
你再说一次"我们的团队"
If you say "part of our team" again,
我就要重新考虑这事
I'll rethink the whole thing.
我愿意
I'll take it.
但我得跟麦克斯先说好
But I have to be upfront with Max.
我不喜欢在后面
I don't like it in the back.
我跟我的男伴们也这么说 我喜欢在"前面"
Which, by the way, is what I say to all my dates.
我也不爱从"后面"
Samesies!
这是个大好消息啊
Well, this is great news.
我们吃块派来庆祝一下吧
How about we celebrate with a piece of pie?
不行
No!
厄尔 我们有个好消息 快猜猜
Earl, we have great news. Guess what it is.
算了别猜 猜吧 别猜了 还是猜吧
No, don't. Okay, guess. No, don't. Yes, guess, guess!
能废话少说吗
Can we hurry this along?
我"表兄"今天上认亲节目
My cousin is on Maury Povich today,
我想看他到底是不是生父
and I wanna find out if he's the father.
如果他是 那孩子的抚养费就没我的事了
'Cause then I can stop paying child support.
抱歉 她有些激动
Sorry. She's a little amped.
她很久没有好消息分享了
She hasn't had good news to share
上一次还是我们发现地下室的
since we found out the washing machine
投币洗衣机纽扣硬币不分
in our basement takes buttons.
阿憨 我们有个好消息
Han! We have good news.
你们肯定有啦
Sure, you do.
我还要去纽约尼克斯队打中锋呢
And I'm playing center for the New York Knicks!
你们有看尼克屎队最近多烂吗
Have you seen the Knicks lately?
他打中锋还帮得上忙呢
He can only help.
根据我的上班考勤卡
Well, according to my time card,
我已经在这里六小时了
I've been here for six hours already,
我要去后面小睡片刻
so I'm gonna head back and catch some Zs.
床垫是你的了 麦克斯
The Mattress is all yours, Max.
抱歉各位 我们没想到会有人要来
Hey, everybody. We weren't expecting company.
我过来跟奥列格讨论一下婚礼细节
I came by to discuss wedding details with Oleg
边交配边讨论
while we had intercourse.
这是哪里 怡红院吗
What is this, the Bunny Ranch?
宝贝 这些好像是你的
Baby, I think these are yours.
是 是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
谢谢你啦 宝贝
Well, thank you, honey.
我们能不能订个基本规矩
Can we just make it a general rule
餐厅里不许行苟且之事
that there's no fornication in the diner?
阿憨的公寓里也不行
Or in Han's apartment, ever.
麦克斯跟我真有一些很棒的好消息
Okay, Max and I have some really exciting news.
是是是 我们都知道纽扣能当硬币投的事
Yeah, yeah. We know all about the buttons.
奥列格
Oleg!
你好像把我的座位表弄坏了
I think you crushed my seating arrangement!
我也希望是被我"玩坏"了
I'd like to think so.
我们要说的是...
So, back to us.
回去工作如何
How 'bout back to work?
我和麦克斯
Max and I...
需要做点工作了
Need to do some work!
就这样 消息报告完毕
There. End of news.
你跑这么快干嘛
Where are you running off to so fast?
有地方在小头特卖 你要买来换掉大头吗
Is someone having a sale on smaller heads?
一下说我小 一下说我大 选好一个行吗
I'm too small, I'm too big--pick one!
我们的大好消息是
Here's our big news.
现在你眼前看着的是
You are looking at the manager
嗨翻天新分店的经理与首席烘焙师
and the head pastry chef of the brand-new High location.
其实他只能看到我们的膝盖吧
Actually, he's looking at our kneecaps.
我猜你们是选我小
Okay, so we're going with too small.
你们走了 我去哪里请胜过你们的人啊
If you two quit the diner, how will I ever replace you?
除非我请了...
Unless I hire...
地球上任何一个人
literally anyone else!
不 阿憨 我们晚上还是会在这里工作啊
No, Han, we still have to work here at night.
我们的债比威尔·史密斯的老婆
We have more debt than Jada Pinkett-Smith
帮他想出的夜不归宿理由还多
has excuses for Will not being home.
但是在嗨翻天
But at the new High,
我们两个就是掌管一切的大哥
we're gonna be the big bosses calling all the shots.
是啊 是啊 早上而已
Yes, yes...by day.
到了晚上 一样是在卷心菜沙拉的魔掌中
But by night, you'll be the coleslaw's bitch.
别听他乱说
Don't listen to him.
阿憨对我们的成功羡慕嫉妒恨
Clearly, Han just resents our success.
就是啊
I know!
女人之间就不能互相为对方开心吗
Why can't women ever just be happy for each other?
这也太辣了
Wow, that is really hot.
是啊
Yeah.
比较不辣的酱在这
The milder salsa's right here.
听我说... 哇
Listen--oh!
女人现在开始吃东西了吗
Do girls eat now?
莉娜·丹恩真是改变了一切啊
Wow! Lena Dunham changed everything!
听我说 你们是哪个跟那个模特睡过
Listen, which one of you is sleeping with the model?
我知道你们其中一个是
I know one of you said you were,
可是你们说话的时候我基本没听
but I don't listen when you talk.
她
She is.
这是个很大的广告计划
This is a massive ad campaign,
我不知道还能用什么措辞
and I don't know how else to say this,
但我需要他的下面看起来大点
but I need his penis to look bigger.
是这样的
Oh! Yeah...
你用光照着它的时候 它会害羞
It gets nervous when you shine a light on it.
有时候我还能听到她用吃的
Sometimes I hear her coaxing it out of its crawl space
来"引蛇出洞"
with treats.
你去做点什么吧
Well, do something.
我大学之后就没碰过那玩意了
I haven't touched one since college,
而大学的那次 也只是翻开来找我的钥匙
and even then it was just to look under it for my keys.
麦克斯 把他带去一边处理 保持专业
Max, take him off set. Be professional.
我是能多保持专业啊
How professional can I be?
她叫我去把他下面弄涨
She's asking me to fluff his nutter.
纳西 休息时间
Yo, Nash! Break time.
玛丽
So...Marie.
乔跟你说过我升职的大事吗
Did Joe tell you about my big new job promotion?
当然说啦 我们是拉拉
Of course she did. We're lesbians.
大多数时间都是在说话
Talking is most of what we do.
所以日间电视是我们的天下
It's why we rule daytime.
抱歉
Eh...pardon me.
你 或许还行... 那风衣 绝对不行
You, maybe. That coat--never.
我在找个人
I'm lookin' for someone.
你还看起来像《天使的孩子》里的龙套呢
You also look like an extra from Angela's Ashes.
但这是私人棚拍
But this is a private shoot,
意思是专拍私处
as in we're shooting someone's privates.
我在找我儿子
I'm looking for me son.
好了 各位 土拨鼠已经出洞了
Okay, people! The groundhog's outta the hole!
再来15公分的冬日
Six more inches of winter.
就是他 那是我儿子
That's him! That's me boy!
妈
Ma?
妈 你怎么会知道我在纽约
Ma, how did you know I was in New York?
你看到我在《今日秀》的窗外围观
Aw, no, you saw me in the Today Show window,
是不是这样
didn't ya?
你的脸书上 在美国签到了
You checked into "America" on Facebook,
你个大傻逼
you bleedin' idiot.
我大老远飞过来没日没夜地
I flew all the way and been lookin' for you day and night
在这个要老命的城市里找了你一周
in this dirty, God forsaken city for a week.
我要把你带回家
I'm takin' you home.
女士 纳西可以自己做决定
Ma'am, Nash can make his own decisions.
他是个大人了
He's a grown man.
是啊 感谢我那一"手绝活"
Yep. Thanks to my handiwork.
他才不是成人 他才十八岁
He's no grown man. He's just now 18.
他下个月还有毕业舞会呢
He's got his prom next month!
我靠 不是吧
I can't believe it!
我跟小屁孩上床了
I had sex with a teenager!
我是谁啊 伍迪·艾伦吗
Who am I, Woody Allen?
罗曼·波兰斯基
Roman Polanski?
我就像70年代大多数的大导演一样
Pretty much any of your big-time '70s movie directors?
你跟我又傻又天真的孩子上床了吗
You had sex with me innocent child?
没多傻多天真好吗
Uh, not so innocent.
他有几次都让我害羞了
He made me blush a few times,
而我可是有两式性爱姿势以我为名的猛女呢
and I have two positions named after me.
够了
Well, that's that.
以后不许再见这个大奶淫娃
You've seen the last of big booby dirty girl here.
我想反驳 可你说对了我无从驳起
I'd object, but when you're right, you're right.
可是妈 我喜欢纽约
But Ma, I like New York.
这里有人想给我小鸡鸡拍照呢
People want to take pictures of me willy here.
这真是我的错
This is all me fault.
我就不应该让你看那个舞男电影《魔力麦克》
I should have never let you watch that Magic Mike.
这下好了
That's great.
我现在没模特了
I don't have a model now.
我成了席尔
I'm Seal.
等着我跟乔说这事吧
Wait until I tell Joe about this.
你怎么可能不知道他几岁啊
How can you not know how old he is?
我能说啥 我们就是典型夫妻啊
Uh...what can I say? We're a typical couple!
他在年龄上撒谎 我假装他说的话很有意思
He lied about his age, and I pretended he was interesting.
好吧 麦克斯 等乔来了
Okay, Max, when Joe gets here,
我就直接跟她说
I'm just gonna tell her
我没管好未成年的奶油小生
that me managing an underage twink
不代表我不能管好她的餐厅
has nothing to do with me managing her restaurant
以及这些定价过高的奶油...蛋糕
which sells overpriced twink...ies.
我相信她一定会用专业的眼光看待此事
Yeah. I'm sure she'll be professional about it all.
专业的眼光
Professional?
昨天她扇了一个女人一耳光
Yesterday, she slapped a woman in here
就因为人家穿了一双廉价高跟鞋
for wearing cheap heels.
我知道 我的脸现在还火辣辣地疼呢
I know. My face is still red.
她来了
Here she is.
早上好 乔
Good morning, Joe!
姑娘们
Hey, ladies.
显然 你们俩被开除了
Well, obviously, you're both fired.
显然是的
Obviously.
我能把帽子留下吗
Can I keep the hat?
你不会想要回它
You are not gonna want this back.
我头上的汗水就像野餐的西瓜一样多水
My head sweats like a watermelon at a picnic.
拜托不要因为纳西的事开除我们
Please don't fire us over the Nash situation.
这件事我们也无法掌控
It was out of our hands.
老实说 这件"事儿"由她手掌控
Actually, it was in her hands,
而且人家才18岁啊
and it was only 18.
你们俩害我女朋友丢脸了
You two embarrassed my girlfriend.
在拉拉界 丢脸这件事
And embarrassment in the lesbian community
比不养狗还要受人鄙视
is worse than not owning a dog.
比跟安妮·海彻约会更糟
It's worse than dating Anne Heche.
天啊 我们犯了海彻罪
Oh, my God. We committed a Heche crime.
我们怎么才能将功补过呢
How can we make it better?
让那个孩子明天回摄影棚拍照
Just get that kid back to the photo shoot tomorrow,
事成之后 你们才能回来工作
and we're back in business.
麦克斯 管好自己
And Max, next time,
不要再碰他不太合法的那"事儿"了
stay out of his barely legal business.
好 不知道怎么办 但好的
Done. Don't know how, but done.
绝不会让你失望
You won't be sorry.
快把他弄回来 因为我不得不说
Just get him back, 'cause I gotta tell ya...
玛丽的哭哭脸
Marie's crying face?
我不喜欢
Not for me.
卷心菜沙拉
Well, coleslaw...
老娘正想退出沙拉江湖
just when I thought I was out,
你又把我拉回来了
you pulled me back in again.
麦克斯 别跟卷心菜沙拉这么说
Max, don't tell the coleslaw that.
别抬举它
Don't give it that power.
我让纳西回去拍照的计划一定会成功
My plan to get Nash back will work.
我们的前途仍一片光明 光芒万丈
We still have a bright, bright future.
是啊 仅限白天
Yes! By day.
阿憨
Han!
你又想在沙拉桶里待一晚是不是
Do you want to spend another night in this coleslaw bucket?
不要
No.
上次我要不是把自己滚到了大街上
And had I not been able to roll myself out to the street,
我说不定就窒息死了呢
I might have suffocated!
纳西和他妈妈随时会来 麦克斯
Nash and his mom will be here any minute, Max.
你真的要露出大半个奶子迎接他们吗
Do you really need to expose 60% of your boobs?
干嘛 这又不是我说了算
What? It's not up to me.
这对姐妹花有她们自己的人生
These girls have a life of their own.
右边那个刚成立了佛利伍麦克翻唱乐团
The right one just started a Fleetwood Mac cover band.
知道我怎么知道的吗
You know how I know?
我一解开胸罩 它就挣脱束缚走自己的路
'Cause when I take my bra off, it goes its own way.
你真的认为你能在他们回来
Do you really think you can get Nash's mother
收拾纳西剩余的东西时
to change her mind when they come in
成功说服他妈妈改变主意吗
to pick up the rest of his stuff?
是的
Yes, I do.
因为她跟我有很多相似的地方
Because she and I have a lot in common.
我或许不是爱尔兰人 但我也一穷二白
I may not be Irish, but I'm dirt poor,
还跟一个爱酗酒的人住在一起
and I'm living with someone who drinks way too much.
麦克斯 看
Max, look.
所有这些紫色的标签
All those purple post-its
都是苏菲的朋友和家人
are Sophie's friends and family.
我根本看不见我的家人在哪儿
My family's nowhere to be seen!
还以为是美国人口普查局的最新分布图呢
It's like I'm looking at the last U.S. Census!
姑娘们 快过来
Hey, girls. Come over here.
我们需要你们帮忙排婚礼座位图
We need your help with the seating chart.
是啊 策划婚礼比满月时
Yeah. You know, planning a wedding is more work
给奥列格后背做蜜蜡除毛费劲多了
than waxing Oleg's back during a full moon.
苏菲 我有自己的问题要操心
Sophie, I have my own issue right now.
好吧 那麦克斯来帮我
Okay. Then Max can help me with the chart
你就去操心你日益减少的头发吧
while you go worry about your obviously thinning hair.
先自我揭露
Uh, full disclosure--
上次有人找我帮忙做某事
the last time someone asked me to help them with something,
他们一半的胡子被我当毒品抽掉了
I free-based half their beard off.
纳西给我发了条短信
I just got a text from Nash.
他来了吗 我给他拿一份儿童菜单
He's here? I'll go get him a kid's menu.
他们不来了
They're not coming.
他妈妈发现我发给他的艳照了
His mom found the racy pictures I sent him.
"明天在肯尼迪机场出发
"Flying out of JFK tomorrow.
搭爱尔兰航空一早的飞机"
Taking the morning Aer Lingus"?
一早就"打"飞机
A little morning "Aer Lingus"?
害麦克斯惹上麻烦的不就是这个吗
Isn't that what got Max in trouble in the first place?
好吧 那我们只好跑去机场
Okay, well, we just have to go to the airport
阻止他们啦
and stop them.
我去买两张飞机票 然后再退了
I'll buy us plane tickets and then return them,
就像我对鞋子那样 或像阿汤哥对老婆们那样
like I do with shoes or Tom Cruise does with wives.
把外套和鞋子脱了
Jackets and shoes off!
检查自己衣服上所有的口袋
And make sure you check all your pockets.
别让我因为一块口香糖就关闭整个机场
Don't make me shut this airport down for a piece of gum.
这队排得比《消失的爱人》电影还长
This line is longer than the movie Gone Girl.
TSA是"时间停止局"的意思吗
What does TSA stand for? "Time Stands A-still?"
这个解释不错 我从来没听过这个
That's cute. Never heard that one before.
大部分人都只是说"太他妈操蛋局"
Most people just go with "This Sucks Ass."
麦克斯 拜托不要大声说话了
Max, please don't yell out again.
人们在机场会变得敏感又神经
People get very jumpy in airports.
干嘛 我又没大声说"我有炸弹"
Oh, what? It's not like I screamed, "I have a bomb!"
小姐 麻烦你到这边来
Miss, will you step over here, please?
我是开玩笑的啦 我没有炸弹
Oh, I was kidding. I don't have a bomb.
但人人都知道我...酷到炸
But I have been known to...be da bomb.
麦克斯
Max!
求你了 如果我们走开
Please, please, if we step away,
这队就白排了
we'll lose our place in line.
我知道听上去我们像是要来炸飞机
I know it sounds like we're here to blow up a plane,
但我们只是来这里阻止一个
but we're really just here to stop an underage kid
跟她发生性关系的未成年孩子离开美国
she had sex with from leaving the country.
所以我还是乖乖过去吧
So I should just come over there now.
是的 恭喜你们入选
Yep. You just been hand-picked
主题为"我不相信你"的舞会
to join the "I don't trust you" dance party.
出示一下你们的机票
May I see your tickets?
天气不错 我喜欢你的发型
Nice day. I like your hair.
谢谢 我们允许在颈部以上
Thanks. We're allowed to be creative
发挥创意
from the neck up.
哇 你们俩居然要飞去巴黎
Ooh! You traveling to Paris.
还是头等舱
First-class.
就穿这种破裤子吗
In those jeans?
你居然买了去巴黎的头等舱机票
You got first-class tickets to Paris?
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
我的手指不由自主嘛
My fingers did it.
上面还留存有富家女的细胞记忆
It was rich girl cellular memory.
而且如果我们哪儿也不去
And if we're not going anywhere,
为什么不能不去巴黎呢
why can't we not go to Paris?
为什么不能不去罗浮宫
And why can't we not go to the Louvre?
为什么不能不待在乔治五世四季酒店的
And why can't we not stay in the penthouse
顶层套间 不点客房服务呢
at the George Cinq and not order room service?
现在说不认识她是不是太晚了
Is it too late for me to say I don't know her?
女士 你有携带任何爆炸物吗
Ma'am, are you carrying any explosives?
我早餐吃了隔夜的墨西哥卷饼
I had leftover Chipotle for breakfast.
这算吗
Does that count?
算 你的屁会炸到坐你旁边的人
It does to whoever's sitting next to you.
法国航空113航班
Air France flight 113
现在开始在24号登机口登机
will now begin boarding at gate 24.
麦克斯 那是我们的航班
Max! That's our flight.
法国航空113航班
Air France, flight 113.
我敢说飞机上
Ooh! I bet on the plane,
一定有鱼子酱和贝利尼鸡尾酒
they'll have caviar and Bellinis.
你知道飞机上一定不会有什么吗
You know what won't be on the plane?
我们
Us!
我们不会上飞机
We're not going!
你是不是偷偷抽了
Have you been smoking the half joint
我藏在胸罩里的大麻烟
I have hidden in my bra?
你居然有大麻烟[联合]
You have a joint?
银行账户
Bank account? Ha!
你居然带着大麻过安检
You went through security with pot?
我还靠[带着]大麻度过三年级呢
I went through third grade with pot.
那边 纳西在那边
There he is. There's Nash.
我敢说她妈一定在问
I'm sure his mom is asking
她儿子能不能进驾驶舱跟机长见面
if he can visit the cockpit and meet the pilot.
哇 他真年轻
Wow. He's young.
他的年纪跟布鲁斯·詹纳
So young, Bruce Jenner has been a woman
变性成女人的年头差不多
for most of his life.
纳西 拜托
Nash! Please.
你不能走 我们整个人生就取决于
You can't go. Our entire lives depend on
你是否完成拍摄
you finishing that photo shoot.
纳西·泰伦斯·奥布赖恩 你不许去
Nash Terrence O'Brien, you're not going anywhere.
否则我要当场把你屁股打开花
Or I'll take you over my knee right here.
他喜欢打屁股
Well, he likes that.
你个...
Well, you...
你还真是一个浪荡女啊 对吗
You are just loose as a goose, aren't ya?
我想反驳 可你说对了我无从驳起
Again...when you're right, you're right.
麦克斯 我来跟奥布赖恩夫人谈吧
Max, let me talk to Mrs. O'Brien.
你去登机口
Go up to the gate.
问问飞机上会播放什么电影
Ask what movie they're showing on their flight.
好的 但如果他们播放任何
Okay, but if they're showing anything,
我是说任何
and I mean anything
亚当·桑德勒的电影
from Mr. Adam Sandler...
那我会毫不犹豫上飞机
I'm getting on the plane too.
拜托 算我求你了
Please. I'm begging you.
你不认识我 我是一个高傲的女人
You don't know me. I'm a proud woman.
我就求过两次人 另外一次是
The only other time I ever begged
求着要离开吹牛老爹的游艇
was to get off of P. Diddy's yacht.
因为哪有派对一开就是开三天的啊
I mean, a party shouldn't be three days long.
小姐 你可以省省你的白痴说辞
Miss, you can save your silly breath.
我要带他回家
I'm taking him home.
乘客梅芙·奥布赖恩请到登机台
Would passenger Maeve O'Brien please report to the gate desk?
纳西 或许他们把我们升舱了
Oh, Nash, maybe they're bumping us up
从经济舱的倒数第一排升到倒数第二排
from the last coach row to the second to the last coach row!
我就知道当初坚持不堕胎终有一天会有回报
I knew I'd be rewarded for not having any abortions
尽管家里已经穷得揭不开锅了
in spite of me circumstances.
抓住纳西 趁她被叫走了
Grab Nash--let's get out of here
我们快离开这
while I got her distracted.
麦克斯 你怎么做到的
Max, you did that? How?
我的大麻烟已经不在我的胸罩里了
I no longer have the half a joint in my bra.
你居然贿赂航班员工 用你的大麻烟[关节]
You bribed an airline employee with a joint?
疼吗 你真应该做做伸展运动
Pain? Oh, you really gotta stretch out for that.
麦克斯 这可是绑架儿童啊
Max, this is kidnapping.
他没那么小啦 我像他那么大的时候
Oh, he's not that young. When I was his age,
我都去音像店抢了三盒录像带了
I had already robbed three Blockbuster videos.
什么是录像带呀
What's Blockbuster video?
天啊 我搞了一个娃
Oh, my God, I screwed a baby.
好了 我要发短信给乔
Okay. I'm gonna text Joe
告诉她纳西在我们手上
and tell her we have Nash in our custody.
算了 还是打电话吧
No, I'd better call.
如果被抓 短信会成为不利证据
That text won't play well at our trial.
抱歉我没告诉你我还小
I'm sorry I didn't tell ya I was so young.
但老实说 我觉得这不重要
But honestly, I didn't think it mattered
因为你也还不够成熟
since you're so immature.
我知道你是 我可不是
I know you are, but what am I?
乔很赞赏我们绑架纳西的行为
Okay, so Joe was really impressed with the kidnapping,
她同意让我们回去工作
and she gave us our jobs back.
但纳西 你被换掉了
But Nash, you've been replaced.
他们找到了另一个模特
They found another model
决不会有父母来找麻烦
who wouldn't give them any parent trouble--
一个大屌孤儿
a well-hung orphan.
大屌孤儿
A well-hung orphan.
上帝赏了他饭碗 又收走了他餐具
Well, the Lord gives and the Lord takes.
那现在是怎样
So what now?
你可以回爱尔兰跟你的朋友吹嘘
Well, you go back to Ireland and brag to your friends
你睡了一个曾经跟艾克索·若斯
about having sex with someone who once had sex
好友的儿子睡过的女人
with Axl Rose's best friend's son.
再见 麦克斯
Good-bye, Max.
回见 纳西小土豆
Later, Nash Potater.
我想我会想念他
You know, I think I'm gonna miss him.
尤其因为奎兹诺斯快餐店6点前小孩免费
Especially since kids eat free at Quiznos before 6:00.
我们快离开这里吧
Let's get out of here.
机场唯一的好处
The only good thing about airports
就是从这里能去往更好的地方
is leaving them for someplace better.
麦克斯 下次我们再来机场之日
Max, next time we're here,
便是我带你去巴黎之时
I'm gonna take you to Paris.
首先麻烦带我去一下洗手间
Well, first take me to the bathroom.
打从我们电车撞到井盖时 我就一直想尿尿
I've had to pee since our tram hit that pothole.
至少我们要去高档的地方工作了
Well, at least we're gonna be working somewhere with class.
真好奇会是哪里
I wonder where it is.
乔说那是一个交通枢纽
Joe said it's a real hub,
旗舰级 国际化
flagship, international.
是啊 地点就在8号"国际"航站楼
Yeah. It's gonna be international terminal 8!
什么
What?
这里吗
Here?
我们要在这里工作吗
We're working here?
我一定要找出上辈子我残忍地杀害了谁
I've got to find out who I brutally murdered
才会落得如此报应 我要去补偿那人
in a previous life and make it up to him or her.
真不爽
This sucks!
这个地方永远不会有人顺路送我们来上班
The one place no one will ever give us a ride to work!
法国航空113航班 最后一次登机广播
Final boarding for Air France, flight 113.
真是时候
Of course it is.
往好的方面想
Look at the bright side.
最近几年 大部分飞机甚至
These days, most planes don't even make it
飞不到目的地
to where they're supposed to go.
头等舱乘客卡洛琳·钱宁和麦克斯·布莱克
Paging first-class passengers Caroline Channing
请尽快登机
and Max Black.
这两个有钱婊真幸运
Those rich bitches are so lucky!